<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers on Morgan Vigil-Hayes</title>
    <link>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Papers on Morgan Vigil-Hayes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LoRaX: Repurposing LoRa as a Low Data Rate Messaging System to Extend Internet Boundaries</title>
      <link>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper4/</guid>
      <description>This paper prototypes the design of a novel network architecture that extends access to Internet services using multihop Low-powered Radio (LoRa) technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A tale of three datasets: characterizing mobile broadband access in the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper2/</guid>
      <description>This paper examines mobile broadband performance data from a measurement campaign in Northern New Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>As a Squash Plant Grows: Social Textures of Sparse Internet Connectivity in Rural and Tribal Communities</title>
      <link>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper5/</guid>
      <description>This paper describes a participatory action research project between several academic institutions and the REDINet network in northern New Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Cultural Relevance into a Behavioral mHealth Intervention for Native American Youth</title>
      <link>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper1/</guid>
      <description>This paper presents findings from participatory design of an mHealth system for Native American youth. Published in CSCW 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complex, Contemporary, and Unconventional: Characterizing the Tweets of the #NativeVote Movement and Native American Candidates through the 2018 U.S. Midterm Elections</title>
      <link>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper3/</guid>
      <description>This paper examines Tweets by and about Native American political candidates during the US 2018 Midterm election cycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#Indigenous: Tracking the Connective Actions of Native American Advocates on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vigil-hayes.github.io/papers/paper6/</guid>
      <description>This paper examines how Native American activists and institutions use Twitter to facilitate connective action during the US 2016 presidential primary election period.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
